DARIA TROFIMOVA

JUNIOR FRONTEND DEVELOPER

CONTACT

telegram: @dartlibre

trofimova.hk@gmail.com

github.com/trofimovadd

Yerevan, Armenia

SKILLS

- JavaScript
- TypeScript
- basic Python
- React
- HTML5
- CSS3
- Firebase
- Flexbox
- GitHub/BitBucket
- Styled Components
- Jest

EDUCATION

Far Eastern Federal University

2017-2021

LANGUAGES

English (C1)

French (A2)

Russian (native)

PROFILE

Diligent and self-taught frontend-developer with 1+ years of experience in commercial application and software development. Capable of continuous learning from senior developers with a desire to apply skills on a larger development team. Eager to solve more complex problems and continue to find ways to increase user experience and user efficiency.

WORK EXPERIENCE

1 year 8 months

Junior Frontend Developer

"RST-Tur", Vladivostok, Russia Russian aggregator of tourist bases and tours

July 2022 - June 2023

- development of adaptive layout of the website using React + TypeScript + styled-components
- · code refactoring and code splitting
- development of new components using atomic design
- · client-side development of the website
- development of new features based on already existing features

Intern Frontend Developer

"RST-Tur", Vladivostok, Russia

Russian aggregator of tourist bases and tours

December 2021 - July 2022

- layout fixing
- code refactoring and code splitting
- interaction with designers and other developers
- · writing the description in README-files to new features

HOBBIES

- learning foreign languages
- reading technical literature (Head First JavaScript by E. Freeman and E. Robson, Clean Code by R. Martin, Grokking algorithms by A. Bhargava, HTML and CSS by J. Dakett, Learning React by A. Banks and E. Porcello)